What up world? It's your boy Nate
Jackson. This is the Super Funny Comedy
Club and this is the Super Funny Comedy
Jam and it's going down live in Tacoma,
Washington. Let me introduce you to this
episode's COMICS. THERE THEY GO.
>> What's going on? This is Re Thomas
coming all the way from Brooklyn, New
York.
[cheering]
>> What's going on? It's Mo Hilling all the
way from Cleveland, Ohio.
>> It's your boy comedian Kelly Kub man.
East Memphis, Tennessee, East Cleveland,
East Milwaukee, East Atlanta. SHOW LOVE.
SHOW LOVE. [cheering] And it's your boy
Smokey Suarez representing Harlem, New
York in the building. [cheering]
Hey [music]
Jack, super funny jam.
>> [singing]
>> jam
[music] jam.
>> What up [cheering] y'all? Hey, this is a
super funny comedy jam. I'm your host,
Nate Jackson. We got some of the
funniest comedies in the country
performing for you live right now. Thank
you for tapping in. We might as well get
into it. We got all kind of people in
here. We got diversity.
>> Yes. Are you a first lady of somebody
church? You look like you blessed.
pressed down, shaking. That's not the
pastor of somebody church right there.
You beautiful, but that's not a pastor.
That's a pastor right there. I know a
pastor when I see one. Like, [\h__\h] I
sell suits, [\h__\h] I ain't a pastor.
Nothing. [\h__\h] I almost miss my wife. I
walk right past her. That's the closest
I got to being a pastor. [\h__\h] out of
here, [\h__\h] I claim all that [\h__\h]
Y'all look good. And what's this? This
is This is uh just two beautiful women.
>> You don't know each other?
>> This my best.
>> That's best.
Damn. Why are women like that? Don't
Don't play.
>> We will hit you with our Dodge Neon.
>> Okay. What you drive since you got to
set the record straight.
>> What kind of Beamer is it? Shout out to
the 3 series.
>> Four.
>> Okay, it's all good. I'm not hating. It
is what it is. It's weird that you had
to make sure we all knew that though. I
want you to know that. Yeah. This going
to play for years. They going to be
like, "That [\h__\h] was in the four
series.
Somebody going to watch this on the
internet in 2035 and throw up. Oh, four
series theory. She need to get her [\h__\h]
together. But we proud of you today.
So that's good. We got some white people
here. How you doing, sir? You got your
arms crossed like we ain't [\h__\h] Like my
career ain't [\h__\h] I need you to relax
before I do a cannonball on you and your
wife. Like you don't think you don't
know who you're [\h__\h] with. I will
grab both my knees and jump off this
stool onto your table and kill everybody
over there. Okay, relax and enjoy
yourself. You look like a Russian
hitman. What? What? What are you? Are
you a white man? What are you?
>> What's your name, sir?
>> Clint, I thought you said some other
[\h__\h]
Cuz I was I thought he was like, "My
name's Clint." I was like, "Wow,
man. You are hard to find."
Y'all ready to start this show? Start.
Make some noise right now. Make some
noise right now. Make some noise right
now. First comment coming to the stage,
Y'ALL. GIVE IT UP FOR REG THOMAS.
What up, man?
It's a nice town. I like this town. It's
not my first time here. It's a vibe. A
little bit of a little homeless problem
out here.
>> And where I'm from, I'm I'm from
Brooklyn. New York, we got a homeless
problem, too.
>> But we've been doing this for a while.
You know what I mean? Like in New York,
we have a very strict no touch policy
with our homeless people. We let them
ask for what they going to ask for. Sing
their songs, dance their dances. Just
don't touch nobody. In Tacoma,
Washington,
they will just hug you.
And it's like, my [\h__\h]
I gave you the money. What is this
about?
And in New York, our homeless people
have more hustle. I was at a Starbucks
the other day and for lack of a better
word, I witnessed the bum off.
[laughter]
This first guy walked to the Starbucks.
HE LIKE, "EXCUSE ME, LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN,
I'M VERY SORRY FOR INTERRUPTING YOUR
DAY."
And out of nowhere, another one walked
in and HE WAS LIKE, "I'M WAY MORE
SORRY." [screaming]
And that's capitalism. That's
competition.
[laughter]
On Valentine's Day, I saw a homeless
couple. They were holding a sign said,
"We have no money. We have no food. All
we have is love and each other."
I was like, "Y'all need to break up."
[laughter]
I feel like you're weighing each other
down.
I do give money though. Like if I walk
around, if I see someone begging for
money, if I got change, I'll give it to
them. Problem is, you can't walk two
blocks without someone begging for
money. And I still give it to them, but
sometimes they beg at the wrong time.
You ever had the homeless guy open the
door for you at the bank?
Now you being slick, my G.
And they all say the same thing. On your
way out.
[laughter]
I'm like, dog, on my way out, I'm going
to have a bunch of 20s on me. What do
you think's about to happen?
Cuz you open this door.
I don't give money to homeless white
people.
Y'all felt that? [laughter]
Y'all felt the room change when I said
that?
I said, "I don't give money to homeless
white people." Y'all looked at me like,
"I never did."
Was that the joke? Cuz we're with you. I
treat them the same way regular white
people treat them. I give them a look of
confusion and disappointment. Like,
you're going to have to get it together.
Me and my girl, we just broke up. We
were together for 4 years. She caught me
cheating once
a month and
accused me of not knowing what loyalty
was. And then she got into a new
relationship and she got dumped for
cheating with me. [laughter]
Silly rabbit. This is when it got toxic.
When she got caught cheating, I was
there for her. I was like, "Yo, I know
what you going through right now."
[laughter]
Now look, you would think telling a
cheating joke at a comedy show is a cool
idea, but most comedy shows are date
night. So I tell a cheating joke and all
the fellas like, "Huh?"
Talk about some other [\h__\h] right now.
But personally, I think cheating jokes
are funny. Fellas, you ever been going
through a breakup and you couldn't tell
your girl?
You just walk around the house sad as
hell.
And you know your girl can read your
energy. She like, "Babe,
what's wrong?
You wouldn't understand."
3 years ago, I got invited to a
Friendsgiving that turned out to be an
orgy
cuz I'm cool. And before I tell y'all
this story, I had no idea that there was
going to be an orgy at the
Friendsgiving. But before that night, I
thought I was an orgy guy.
Most guys in our heads, we think we're
org ready.
Let OG break out, see what I do. I
[\h__\h]
You ain't going to do none of that [\h__\h]
That was me. And then an org broke out
over dinner and I was like, who the [\h__\h]
are you people for real? BY THE KEY PIE,
40 people at the orgy. I was the only
black guy.
So much white sex.
Yuck. [laughter] I had no idea white
people get that pink. It was like
staring INTO THE SUN.
I describe it as a violet fuchsia.
[\h__\h] looked like a lava lamp. Lot of
different vibes at orgy. A lot of
different personalities. There's the
girl having aggressive orgasms, but no
one believes her. She like, "John,
John." But we all watching
and John not even pumping like that.
That was a night I learned white boys
[\h__\h] with their shoulders and not their
hips. John was going
I was like John's going to kill someone.
And even though I was freaked out I was
freaked out but I stayed for 8 hours.
Why' I do that?
Cuz I could not stop watching.
Eventually I started to walk around the
orgie like a sensei who was really
impressed with his class.
little tart.
[cheering]
>> True story. 6 months later, I got booked
to tell some jokes on all black orgy.
The black orgy was way more lit. They
were playing better music, but you know,
black customer service could leave a lot
to be desired. They were playing better
music, but they didn't pay for the
premium Pandora.
So the whole or you you hear some smooth
music, then you hear liberty, liberty,
liberty, liberty. Yo, that's my time. My
name's Re Thomas. Thank you very much.
One more time for Re Thomas.
Re like he's like he supposed to have on
glasses.
[laughter]
He said, "I looked at the sun." And I
was like, "Yeah, Ray Charles." Yes, you
did.
[laughter]
Listen, I'm about to have been in this
comic cup immediately. So, start making
noise right now. Start making noise
right now. Start [music] making noise
right now. Y'all give it up for Mo Hill.
Yeah. Y'all look good as hell in here
tonight. Got all kind of people. Young
people, old people, [\h__\h]
Where my middle-aged people at? Make
some noise. My middle age people.
Middle-aged people. Make some noise.
Yeah. All right.
Terrible. Love my middle-aged people,
man. Y'all some of my favorite people,
man. Y'all some my favorite people, but
y'all suck at technology.
Y'all are the worst texters in the
[\h__\h] world. Y'all need to figure
these phones the [\h__\h] out. If you want a
good answer from a middleways person,
you got to call them. You can't text
them cuz they don't know how to [\h__\h]
respond. I text my dad the other day. I
text my dad. I said, "Dad, we about to
go to lunch. Where you want to go?" This
[\h__\h] replied, "Yes."
[laughter]
Then his next text was three eggplant
emojis.
[laughter]
For those that don't know, them the dick
emojis. So now I'm confused. I text him
back. I said, "Dad, what is this?" He go
say, "Oh, my bad. I meant to send that
to your mama." "What? Give me the
phone."
So, he blocked cuz a dickpick might be
next. I can't get no dickpick from my
dad. That's going to change the
relationship. Last thing, I wanted to
get a dickpick from my dad. And I found
out this [\h__\h] got a weew wee. Oh my
god. My dad got a [\h__\h] weew wee. Is
it hereditary? [\h__\h] [laughter]
Love my dad though. But he at that age
where he want to say what he want to say
when he want to say it. That's
middle-aged people. Y'all say what's on
y'all mind. Y'all don't give a [\h__\h] the
time, place. Y'all don't give a [\h__\h] who
listening. I'm not there yet. I'm still
in my mid30s. I give a [\h__\h] He don't
care. We went to lunch. It was me, him,
and the people that work there.
That's it.
Out of nowhere, my dad going to whisper
to me out loud.
Cuz middle-aged [\h__\h] can't whisper to
save their goddamn life. You ever heard
a middle-aged man whisper? They whisper
through their teeth. Look, look, look,
look, look, look, look, look, look,
look, look. Then when you can't hear
them, they get physical. LOOK, LOOK,
LOOK, LOOK. [\h__\h] I heard you. You can
knock my shoulder out OF THE PLACE. SAY
IT OUT LOUD. [laughter]
My dad going to whisper to me out loud.
It's some [\h__\h] in here. Dad, we ain't
Popeyes. What the [\h__\h] is you doing?
These little hoes got fat asses, [\h__\h]
They can hear you. I don't give a [\h__\h]
I'm 65. That's
love my dad though, man. Learn to laugh
from my dad. That's why I like to try to
stay in shape. I do like staying in
shape. The problem is when you work out,
your friends think you supposed to help
them fight.
My friends think cuz I work out I'm
supposed to be their backup
>> and they find out every single time I'm
the first to back the [\h__\h] up. I'm not
fighting nobody. I'm not fighting. I
know it look like I'm the [\h__\h] in the
crew that be like, I see you outside.
No, [\h__\h] I don't see you in court. I'm
not. No. You think I do shoulder
workouts to be cute? No. So I hold my
hand up longer in court, your honor. I
saw the whole thing. Them [\h__\h] did
that [\h__\h] I'll be in court like a bad
[\h__\h] I don't give a [\h__\h]
Them [\h__\h] did that [\h__\h]
I'm not fighting no [\h__\h] about it. When
you get to a certain age, you can't be
fighting no more. Especially when you
get to your 30s, you definitely can't be
fighting no more. And I'm going to tell
you why. Cuz your breathing change.
Your wind is not the same when you get
to your 30s. Can't be tussling with
people. Some of y'all got lightheaded
walking to your seat. You think you
going to tussle? What's the [\h__\h]
about? You going to take your shirt off
tonight and see dots in the air and you
think you going to tussle?
Sit your ass down. [laughter]
Work out to be single, man. It's hard
being single out here. It's too many
rules. Too many rules in relationship,
especially being single. Too many rules.
One rule I learned recently is if you go
to somebody house for a one night stand
and you wake up and they made breakfast
for one, time to get your [\h__\h] leave.
Get your [\h__\h] and go home. I learned
this the hard way. I went to this girl's
house one time. I had a one night stand.
I was so drunk I gave her the worst dick
of my life. I woke up. This [\h__\h] had
one egg and one waffle on the plate. Do
y'all know how embarrassing it is? My
dick game couldn't get an extra egg in
that skillet. It's 12 in a carton.
[\h__\h] you couldn't put one more in the
skillet. [cheering] That's when I
learned your dick game determine what
kind of breakfast you get.
And that's why some of y'all quiet cuz
you can't get avocado toast.
It's a [\h__\h] in the back right now like,
"Damn, that do make sense."
I was wondering why she gave me oatmeal
with no water in it. [\h__\h] you tried to
kill me. [\h__\h] you tried to kill me
over some breakfast dick. [\h__\h] old
[\h__\h] get mad. They start talking [\h__\h]
[\h__\h] I had all kind of waffles and
eggs in 79. [\h__\h] I had omelets with
three teases. [\h__\h] you didn't know.
Oh, Otis got the dick. All right, y'all.
That's been my time. My name is Mohill.
>> [cheering]
>> Thank you. [music] That was Mo Hill. Hey
man, the next meeting in the comment.
Hey, this my homeboy. Y'all make some
noise for Kelly Kub.
[music]
Show love. Show some love, man.
I like y'all. Y'all got good energy. God
damn it. That's what I'm talking about.
>> [applause]
>> Make some noise if your check engine
light on in your car right now. Make
some noise. Clap it up. Show love. [\h__\h]
that check engine light. You still drive
that [\h__\h] every day. Clap it up. Make
some noise. That check engine light.
Goddamn it. [\h__\h] that check engine
light. I bought it with the check engine
light on. I'm going to sell it with the
check engine light on. Make some noise.
If you got a crack in your windshield,
you still drive the [\h__\h] out of it. Make
some noise. [cheering] Real talk. Clamp
it up. Your cell phone crack. Make sure
you got a crack in your cell phone. You
still talk [\h__\h] on that cell phone. Tell
people they ain't [\h__\h] every day on
their cell phones. Make some noise if
you got a brown toenail. Clap it up. One
of your toenails yellow. Clap it up. You
got a yellow toenail on your feet. Make
some noise right now. You a beat a
[\h__\h] W in the grocery store.
Open toe thong sandal. Toenail out. [\h__\h]
it. This brown been brown. Don't nobody
want to clap. Make some noise. If you
sleep with somebody with a brown
toenail, you lay with them every night.
That's your boo. I'm talking about you
got kids by them. Your kids was born
with brown toenails. Make some noise.
You got a little brown toenail, child.
That little brown toenail will beat the
[\h__\h] out you. A [\h__\h] with a
brown toenail slap the [\h__\h] out your
ass, man. I ain't never seen a
[\h__\h] with a brown toenail lose a
fight, man. [\h__\h] with a brown
toenail will choke the [\h__\h] out you. I'm
talking about put that thumb in your
throat. I ain't talking about no regular
choke. I'm talking about press that
thumb right up in your throat, [\h__\h] I
seen somebody with a brown toenail come
skip the line at the grocery store just
and ain't nobody say [\h__\h] He walk right
to the front, put his [\h__\h] on the
counter. I was in that line, too. I
ain't say [\h__\h] either.
I said, "Let that [\h__\h] pay for that
limarine pie and let them get on out of
here, man. That's all he trying to do.
[cheering] Pay for that little limarine
pie. Get your life all the way together,
man. I don't give a [\h__\h] who you are.
Get your [\h__\h] together."
You ever compliment somebody and they
take it too far? [laughter] You weren't
really trying to say all that. You
complimenting, they take it too far. You
be like, "I like this spaghetti." "Yeah,
I was thinking about opening up a
business." "Oh, hell no, [\h__\h] This
[\h__\h] is not. Do not go get a LLC for
this old sweet ass dry ass spaghetti.
Ain't nobody about to buy this goddamn
sticky ass spaghetti. [\h__\h] what you
put in here? Jelly. This [\h__\h] sweet and
sticky. What the [\h__\h] you put in here?
This some grit ass spaghetti you got
right here. People ain't [\h__\h] Make some
noise if you ever put some drawers in a
bag and throw them away. [\h__\h] the
washer. [\h__\h] the dryer. Get these
drawers out of here, man. I ain't about
to put them in the washer with some
clothes. I ain't about to put them in
there self. God damn it. So, I'm just
going to put them in a bag. Time it out.
Put them in another bag. Throw them on
top of somebody house. Make some noise.
[\h__\h] these draws. Clap it up. You done
threw some draws away. Ain't nobody
going to clap. [\h__\h] these draws, man.
Time in a knot. Put them in a bag. Time
in another knot. Throw them on the back
of somebody truck. Let them drive off
with them. [\h__\h] these draws. We throw
draws away, man. [\h__\h] these drawers. I
ain't never seen nobody watch a little
shitty pair of draws, throw them in the
drive. We just get rid of them, take it
down to the gas station, throw them in
their garbage. You don't put them in
your own garbage. You do not put draws
in your own garbage. You'll take them
down to the family dollar. Throw them in
their garbage. [\h__\h] that.
Take them down anywhere. I don't give a
[\h__\h] I ain't put them in my own
garbage. I'm take them somewhere.
You don't put them in your own garbage.
It be just your luck. You put them in
your own garbage. The dog come out there
and tatty garbage up that night. Now
your draws over there in the neighbor
yard.
You got some dirty ass neighbors to
bring your draws back to you on a stick.
He got your draws on a stick, sir.
I found your drawers on the side of my
house. On the side by my air
conditioning unit. You said what? I said
your drawers around the side of my house
by my air conditioning unit. [laughter]
Who draws in them? They your drawers.
That's what I'm trying to tell you. Is
this a trail of trash running from your
mailbox to the surrounding side of my
house by my air conditioning unit? How
the [\h__\h] you know they my draw? That's
what I'm trying to tell you. I got a
camera system pointed right at your
house. You can see where the dogs throw
the garbage up. They tore it up and tore
around the side of my house by the air
conditioning unit. Where the footage at?
That's what I'm saying. If you look
right here, you can see where the dog is
tear the garbage up and then they put
into the drawers right there. You can
see where they ran off. It's about 4:27
a.m. But one of the dogs took the
drawers on the side of my house by my
air conditioning unit.
Man, give me the goddamn draws, man. Get
the [\h__\h] away from my goddamn house.
That's early in the goddamn morning.
Hey man. Hey man. Y'all have a great
night. I'm comedian K D. Y'all holler.
Holla. Holla. Show love. Show some love.
Show love. [cheering]
That [\h__\h] went crazy just that
[\h__\h] said, "I found your draw. I got
your draw." You took the draws off the
stick. [laughter]
I like his draw. Hilarious. One more
time for Kelly Kub. [cheering]
How about that same energy? Let's keep
that rolling. Let's keep that rolling.
Let's keep that rolling. More. More.
More. All the way from Harlem, New York.
Y'all give it up for Smokey Sar.
[music]
Give it up for all the ladies. Give it
up for yourselves. Clap. [music]
Especially, you got to watch out for the
new ladies, fellas. We got to be careful
for the new ladies cuz they outside and
they dressing sexy. I had to tell this
lady the other day there. I was like,
"Miss, your balls is hanging from under
your dress."
>> Yeah, the Transformers is out here,
fellas.
Yeah, you got to watch out.
Back in the days, you knew it was a
Transformer cuz they had an Adams Apple.
So, you be like, "Yo, that's a nigga."
Now technology is different. Now, you
can shave that [\h__\h] off with the iPhone.
They got the shave the bump off your
neck app. $49.99.
I'm scared to meet woman now. And I
ain't going to lie, fell. I'm scared to
meet woman. You know what I do when I
meet woman now? I put a Viagra in her
drink
and I wait 30 minutes and if that
sundress pop up.
Hey yo, Kesha, what the [\h__\h] is that?
Yo, I meant to talk to you about that.
I don't mind gay people. I ain't going
to lie. I'm scared of the new gay women
though. The the little shmean chicks.
You know what I'm talking about. They be
in the club. [\h__\h] you looking at my girl
FOR LIKE, [\h__\h] I'LL PUNCH YOU IN YOUR
SPORTS, BRO. They wonder why dudes
wearing skinny jeans. These [\h__\h] took
all the 34s right now. We walk around
with yeast infections and [\h__\h] I got a
mussy, a man [\h__\h]
A mussy.
Fellas, make some noise if you outside.
If you over 50, make some noise.
[cheering] Yeah, it suck when you get
old cuz the first thing to go when you
get old is your nuts. [laughter]
Nut. Yeah, your nuts are like titties,
[\h__\h] Word up. [\h__\h] like titties.
Word up. You can't even [\h__\h] no more
when you over 50. You got to hold your
nuts in your hand. [laughter]
You flush the toilet, your [\h__\h] balls
in the basement.
[cheering] That's how I knew I was
getting old. That was the first thing I
knew cuz my nuts changed. My nuts used
to be beautiful. My nuts used to look
like grapes, [\h__\h] The green grapes
with the water driplets.
Now my nuts look like some sunny listing
boxing gloves.
I ain't going to lie. But the pandemic
helped me though. I ain't going to lie.
Cuz I went and got a PPP loan.
>> Yeah. And I ain't [\h__\h] that money up.
You know what I did? I went to Dominican
Republic and I got some new nuts.
I got a BBL ladies. A Brazilian ball
lift.
When you get old, [\h__\h] change. Your body
change. You can't do the same [\h__\h] you
used to do. I used to [\h__\h] off of fast
music. Any kind of music. It do to make
a thing. All right.
It do to make it outside.
Now my [\h__\h] changed. My [\h__\h] old. I'm
like, let's get it on.
Let's get it on my dick like a Tootsie
Roll commercial. And the one and the
two.
I don't even pump no more. I just let
the dick soak.
You can't be wasting your [\h__\h] fellas.
You You can't do the same [\h__\h] when you
all Word up. Like I used to nut. I ain't
going to lie. I used to nut. My nut was
ridiculous when I was young. I nut ALL
OVER THE PLACE. W
nut on the cat.
[\h__\h] you nut on me for
now? I'm older. My nut ch like I ain't
going to lie. I nut my nut like a period
now.
Yeah. Like I I bust a nut every 30 days
like a period. I'll be spotting. I'll be
like, "Oo,
my nut about to drop."
Where the ladies at? Make some noise.
Give it up for y'all
with a job. If y'all got a job,
[cheering]
if you making a couple of dollars, clap
right now. If you making a couple of
dollars,
fellas, pay attention to who making a
couple of dollars. Cuz that's all a
woman give a [\h__\h] about is a couple of
dollars.
Where the ladies at. One more time with
the clean house.
Fellas, you can't be [\h__\h] with these
young chicks cuz these young chicks look
good, but they don't clean their house.
>> Yeah, you know you are. I went to one
girl house. You know the fly traps,
>> the sticky [\h__\h]
>> This [\h__\h] had a mouse hanging from it.
>> [\h__\h] is that a mouse on your ceiling?
>> And I hate to go to girl's house. Y'all
got roaches and act surprised like you
never seen a roach in your house. SHE
LIKE, "OOH, I DON'T KNOW who roaches
these is, but these are not my roaches."
[\h__\h] he got two pieces of ID with your
address.
That's your [\h__\h] roach. He grew up in
this apartment. [cheering]
You can tell when girls got roaches in
their house too, right? You can tell it
always happen when you [\h__\h]
[laughter] cuz you be concentrating. You
You focus. You butt naked. You focus.
You concentrating. Do you see the rose
go?
I don't know who roers these.
And roaches got ethnic groups. You can
tell the roasters got ethnic groups,
right?
Black roast walk straight through living
room. [laughter]
I just got this suit out the cleanest
[\h__\h]
You can tell the Spanish roast cuz
that's the fast roach. That's the roach
you step on. BABY, I ATE your meal.
J can't get me now. J can't get me now.
Got to have a white roast, too. Give it
up for white people cuz you know y'all
nosy. Y'all see all the other roaches
getting killed but y'all still want to
check it out.
The [\h__\h] is going on down there?
My owners are crackhead to the fifth
power.
You can't even sleep around this [\h__\h]
This [\h__\h] is steal your dreams. Dreams
for sale. $5.
I got TWO POKING NOSE AND A BERMUDA.
[laughter]
YOU EVER HAD A CRACK ASS FAMILY MEMBER?
They steal [\h__\h] that you can't find,
right? Like I gotta ask for Scrabble.
How you find S's? [laughter]
You ever have that crackhead family
member embarrass your ass? Yeah. All
day. Like you walking down the street,
your new girl, she pop out the bushes.
NEPHEW, [laughter]
[cheering]
let me get a dollar.
Cracker has invented the Harlem Shake.
Yeah. Yeah. The first crack had to hit
some crack. That was like
[laughter]
[cheering]
my aunt. Yo, like I said, we couldn't
take this [\h__\h] nowhere. I ain't going
to lie. We for This is a true story. We
took her to a pet shop. This [\h__\h] tried
to steal a bird.
What?
Look, I came in here with this bird.
I always have.
[laughter]
>> Yo, give it up for yourself. That's my
boy N joke. [cheering]
Smoky Suarez, y'all. Hey. [cheering]
Hey y'all. Keep it going for Mo Hill,
[applause]
Kelly Kell, Rich Thomas. That's our
episode, y'all. I'll see y'all next
week.
[cheering]
[music]